Kim A Brandt

Web Developer

206.719.5217 kimmabrandt@gmail.com github.com/kimmabrandt linkedin.com/in/kimmabrandt Seattle, WA

I am a web developer and experienced graphic designer who has always had a passion for technology and digital media. I am a critical and creative thinker, and am enthusiastic about learning new concepts. My organization skills and ability to successfully work with others on collaborative projects make me a great addition to any team.

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Ruby, SQL

Frameworks and Libraries: Angular, jQuery, Ruby on Rails, Node, Express, Phaser, Bootstrap,

Materialize

Databases and ORMs: PostgreSQL, Sequelize, MongoDB

Software / Other: Git / Github, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Corel DRAW, 3D Studio

Max

Visual Communication: Print design, brand identity, digital and film photography

Projects

PixaPost

An image sharing app geared towards artists or designers, where users can browse, save, or share inspiring images. Image feed is generated by pulling images via Tumblr API. Users can add images to their personal favorites gallery.

Technologies: Express, Node.js, AJAX, Javascript, Sequelize, Facebook API/Oauth, Heroku, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, Tumblr API

Kitty Combat

An arcade style platformer game created with the Phaser.io framework. Included custom graphics and spritesheets.

Technologies: Phaser.io, Javascript, HTML, CSS

MvPetPal

Worked in a team of 4 to create a virtual pet app/game. User can perform various activities (feed, play, sleep, etc) and 'pet' responds accordingly. Created custom spritesheets and CSS animations.

Technologies: Angular, Javascript, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML5, CSS3, Heroku

Experience

Web Development Immersive / Student **General Assembly** Sep 2016 - Dec 2016

3 month intensive bootcamp covering front and back end web development.

- Worked on teams as well as solo to build fully functional, dynamic web pages and apps
- Completed 4 project web apps from scratch which include RESTful routes, databases, and responsive design up to coding standards
- Extensive work with Javascript and JS frameworks, along with Ruby on Rails, databases and ORMs, version control, HTML/CSS, and more

Graphic Designer / Sales Associate

Signs of Seattle May 2013 - Sep 2014 | **McNamara Signs** Oct 2014 - June 2016 Worked closely with business clients and consumers to create custom artwork and assist with signage sales. Projects include interior and exterior signage, vehicle graphics, and other visual and display projects.

- Consistently one of the highest performing sales representatives
- Received positive feedback and commendations from many customers
- Clients include: University of WA, Microsoft, Boeing, Artisan Electric, Nucor Steel, Imperial Parking, WA Trails Association, and many other large and small companies

Freelance Graphic Designer

2008 - Present

Self employed freelance web and graphics business, designing print and web materials including name tags, certificates, flyers, brochures, advertisements, event displays, greeting cards and websites for various clients.

Education

General Assembly, Dec 2016 Web Development Immersive

Western Washington University, July 2010 B.A. Communications | Emphasis: Internet Studies